[
  {
    "userId": "000000000000000000000001",
    "recurringCorrect": 0,
    "totalQuestions": 0,
    "totalRight": 0,
    "questions": [
      { 
        "number": 1,
        "question": "tha mi (ha mee)",
        "answer": "I am",
        "next":1,
        "m":1
      },
      { 
        "number": 2,
        "question": "tha i (ha ee)",
        "answer": "she is",
        "next":2,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "tha e (ha a)",
        "answer": "he is",
        "next":3,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "tha sinn (ha sheen)",
        "answer": "we are",
        "next":4,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "tha sibh (ha sheev)",
        "answer": "you are",
        "next":5,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "fuar (foour)",
        "answer": "cold",
        "next":6,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "an la (un lla)",
        "answer": "the day",
        "next":7,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "blath (bplah)",
        "answer": "warm",
        "next":8,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "am bata (um bpatu)",
        "answer": "the boat",
        "next":9,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "oidhche (oichu)",
        "answer": "night",
        "next":10,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 11,
        "question": "sqoil (sgoll)",
        "answer": "school",
        "next":11,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 12,
        "question": "bha mi (va mee)",
        "answer": "I was",
        "next":12,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 13,
        "question": "na coin (nu ko-yn)",
        "answer": "the dogs",
        "next":null,
        "m":1
      }
    ],
  "head": 0
  },
  {
    "userId": "000000000000000000000002",
    "recurringCorrect": 0,
    "totalQuestions": 0,
    "totalRight": 0,
    "questions": [
      { 
        "number": 1,
        "question": "tha mi (ha mee)",
        "answer": "I am",
        "next":1,
        "m":1
      },
      { 
        "number": 2,
        "question": "tha i (ha ee)",
        "answer": "she is",
        "next":2,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "tha e (ha a)",
        "answer": "he is",
        "next":3,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "tha sinn (ha sheen)",
        "answer": "we are",
        "next":4,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "tha sibh (ha sheev)",
        "answer": "you are",
        "next":5,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "fuar (foour)",
        "answer": "cold",
        "next":6,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "an la (un lla)",
        "answer": "the day",
        "next":7,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "blath (bplah)",
        "answer": "warm",
        "next":8,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "am bata (um bpatu)",
        "answer": "the boat",
        "next":9,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "oidhche (oichu)",
        "answer": "night",
        "next":10,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 11,
        "question": "sqoil (sgoll)",
        "answer": "school",
        "next":11,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 12,
        "question": "bha mi (va mee)",
        "answer": "I was",
        "next":12,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 13,
        "question": "na coin (nu ko-yn)",
        "answer": "the dogs",
        "next":null,
        "m":1
      }
    ],
  "head": 0
  },
  {
    "userId": "000000000000000000000003",
    "recurringCorrect": 0,
    "totalQuestions": 0,
    "totalRight": 0,
    "questions": [
      { 
        "number": 1,
        "question": "tha mi (ha mee)",
        "answer": "I am",
        "next":1,
        "m":1
      },
      { 
        "number": 2,
        "question": "tha i (ha ee)",
        "answer": "she is",
        "next":2,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "tha e (ha a)",
        "answer": "he is",
        "next":3,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "tha sinn (ha sheen)",
        "answer": "we are",
        "next":4,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "tha sibh (ha sheev)",
        "answer": "you are",
        "next":5,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "fuar (foour)",
        "answer": "cold",
        "next":6,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "an la (un lla)",
        "answer": "the day",
        "next":7,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "blath (bplah)",
        "answer": "warm",
        "next":8,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "am bata (um bpatu)",
        "answer": "the boat",
        "next":9,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "oidhche (oichu)",
        "answer": "night",
        "next":10,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 11,
        "question": "sqoil (sgoll)",
        "answer": "school",
        "next":11,
        "m":1
      },
      {
        "number": 12,
        "question": "bha mi (va mee)",
        "answer": "I was",
        "next":12,
        "m":1
      }, 
      {
        "number": 13,
        "question": "na coin (nu ko-yn)",
        "answer": "the dogs",
        "next":null,
        "m":1
      }
    ],
  "head": 0
  }
]